OTHMAN SEMLALI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



+212 657-522351

othmansemlali23@gmail.com

Q Lot El fadle, Casablanca

semlali.tech

SKILLS

- PHP, Javascrip, Typescript, Python
- Laravel
- Node Js
- Express Js
- Database Management
- Jira Software

LANGUAGES

- French: Limited
- English: professional

EDUCATION

DIGITAL DEVELOPMENT

ISTA

2021 - 2023

PHYSICAL SCIENCES

Hassan II University

2018 - 2020

PHYSICAL SCIENCES BACCALAUREATE

Mousa ibn noussair 2017 - 2018

PROFILE

Junior Full Stack Web Developer with a strong experience in PHP and JavaScript. Skilled in developing and maintaining web applications from front to back. Ability to adapt to new technologies and work well in collaborative environments

EXPERIENCE

MERN STACK DEVELOPER

Ark-x Talent Factory

01/2024 - Present

- Demonstrated expertise in MERN stack development, with handson experience in building scalable and responsive web applications.
- · Adept at working in Agile/Scrum methodologies.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - FREELANCE

mostaqil

2022 - 2023

- Database administration and website design
- Developed a dynamic and user-friendly e-commerce platformEducational institutions and online classroom management
- Developed and deployed a dynamic authentication system, strengthening security protocols.

CERTIFICATE

AGILE WITH ATLASSIAN JIRA

coursera

07/2023

https://coursera.org/share/0acd3eb751a07fc5f34a1edbffb96e30